Sportspectrum UP011
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Sportspectrum
1985 -- 1989
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Athletics Department
UP011
2 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of issues of the Sportspectrum which was a monthly student magazine containing player interviews, highlights and detailed analysis of both Tufts and non-Tufts sports. The magazine was published from November 1985 - October 1989.
- Sportspectrum, 1985 -- 1989; UP011.001; 2 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains bound volumes of Sportspectrum, a monthly magazine containing player interviews, highlights and detailed analysis of both Tufts and non-Tufts sports. The magazine was published from November 1985 - October 1989.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Sportspectrum, 1985-11; UP011.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1985-12; UP011.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1986-02; UP011.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1986-03; UP011.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1986-04; UP011.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1986-11; UP011.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1986-12; UP011.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1987-03; UP011.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1987-04; UP011.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1987-10; UP011.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, Spring, 1988; UP011.001.001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
  - Sportspectrum, 1988-10; UP011.001.002.00001 (Box Volume 2)
  - Sportspectrum, 1989-01; UP011.001.002.00002 (Box Volume 2)
  - Sportspectrum, 1989-03; UP011.001.002.00003 (Box Volume 2)
  - Sportspectrum, 1989-10; UP011.001.002.00004 (Box Volume 2)